http://www.coopervision.com/privacy-policy

Myopia Management
About Contact LensesHandling your contact lensesHow to put your contact lenses in
Leadership
Global newsCooperVision Announces the Opening of new site in Costa Rica
Privacy policy
This site is governed solely by applicable U.S. laws and governmental regulations. Please see our Privacy Policy. Use of this site constitutes your consent to application of such laws and regulations and to our Privacy Policy. Your use of the information on this site is subject to the terms of our Legal Notice. To contact us, use the Contact Us section or use the Comments capability at the end of each post.PRIVACY POLICY:
This site is owned by CooperVision, Inc. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site.Your Consent
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.About Children
This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this site from visitors under that age.Information You Provide
This site may ask you to submit personally identifiable information in order for you to submit comments to the site, to purchase goods or request customer service.Passive Information Collection
As you navigate through this site, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). Your Internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the Web site you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without
cookies.
This site may use such passively collected anonymous information to provide better service to site visitors, customize the site based on your preferences, compile and analyze statistics and trends, and otherwise administer and improve the site for your use.
Find the right lens
Get your free trial
Find an eye doctor
Current rebates
Join us on Facebook
MyDay family
MyDay
MyDay toric
Can't find your brand?
